(Raj:)Feel better now?
It's indigenous to Brazil, as is the cocoa
bean from which we get chocolate.
(Sheldon:)You promised
you wouldn't do that anymore.
- Hey, Hofstadter.
- Hey, Kripke.
Heard about your anti-proton
decay experiment.
Twenty thousand data runs
and no statistically significant results.
Very impressive.
(Howard:)What a jerk.
(Raj:)Don't feel bad, Leonard.
Negative results are still results.
- Even 20,000 of them.
- All right.
(Leonard:)Please don't cheer me up anymore.
Come on, don't let him get to you.
It's Kripke.
(Raj:)Yeah, he's a ginormous knob.
(Howard:)That's why he eats by himself
instead of sitting here at the cool table.
For shizzle.
(Sheldon:)Hey, it's true, Kripke lacks the basic
social skills that we take for granted.
But he controls
the new Open Science Grid computer...